<resources>
    <!-- Title of App -->
    <string name="app_name">Leeds Centre Tour Guide</string>

    <!-- Trinity Centre category -->
    <string name="category_trinity">Trinity Centre</string>

    <string name="trinity_entrance">The Trinity Shopping Centre is located on Albion Street in Leeds,
        West Yorkshire, UK. It is named after the 18th-century Holy Trinity Church that it is
        adjacent to. The centre is open 9am-8pm Monday-Saturday and until 5pm on Sundays.</string>

    <string name="trinity_kitchen">The Trinity Kitchen is a unique spin on typical shopping centre
        food courts. In addition to permanent outlets, the Kitchen features 5 street food vans on a
        6-8 week rotating basis, offering visitors a constantly changing culinary experience.</string>

    <string name="trinity_art">Two of the best known art sculptures in the Trinity Centre are
        \'Equus Altus\' and \'Minerva\' by Andy Scott, but from security gates to graffiti murals and
        even benches, you can find art around every corner.</string>

    <string name="trinity_entertainment">In addition to the Kitchen, Leeds Trinity has several
        restaurants and cafés throughout the centre. There is literally something for everyone! After
        you eat, you can relax on a sofa at Everyman Cinema and watch a blockbuster film. </string>

    <string name="trinity_events">There\'s always something happening at Leeds Trinity Centre! From
        Running Clubs to Chocolate Tasting, Flash Mob performances to Gin Festivals, you never know what
        might happen from one day to the next!</string>


    <!-- Belgrave Music Hall category -->
    <string name="category_belgrave">Music Hall</string>

    <string name="belgrave_entrance">The Belgrave Music Hall is located at Cross Belgrave Street in
        Leeds. Originally a rec hall and nursery school, the building has been totally restored and
        has become one of the go to places in Leeds.</string>

    <string name="belgrave_roof_garden">The roof terrace is a popular hangout spot during the summer.
        With a small bar at one end so you don\'t have to go downstairs to the main bar to get drinks,
        you can relax on the faux grass turf and take in the views of the city centre.</string>

    <string name="belgrave_food">The Music Hall boasts two different places to eat and neither will
        break the bank. Dough Boys offers handmade pizza with ingredients sourced locally while
        Patty Smith\'s does burgers and chips which will keep you full for the rest of the day!</string>

    <string name="belgrave_canteen">The Canteen is full of comfortable sofas and chairs as well as
        picnic style tables. The overall atmosphere invites you to sit down, relax, and enjoy the
        music that is always playing.</string>

    <string name="belgrave_events">As expected, the Music Hall puts on music gigs and screens classic
        films. In addition to this, they also host weekly Yoga classes, monthly Street Food \'Feast\'
        days, as well as Retro Games nights.</string>

    <!-- Kirkgate Market category -->
    <string name="category_market">Kirkgate Market</string>

    <string name="market_entrance">Leeds Kirkgate Market is open Monday-Saturday from 8am-5:30pm.It
        boasts over 170 traders with a food hall and a bustling outdoor market. Kirkgate Market can be
        found at Vicar Lane near the Corn Exchange.</string>

    <string name="market_food_hall">Located in the 1976 Hall of the Market, the Food Hall is a large
        open space with several Street Food style cafés around the perimeter. The Food Hall also hosts
        various performances and craft markets throughout the year.</string>

    <string name="market_education">In cooperation with famous chef Jamie Oliver, Kirkgate market is
        home to Jamie\'s Ministry of Food, a charity run venue which holds cooking classes suitable for
        every skill level.</string>

    <string name="market_history">Kirkgate Market opened in 1857 and was designed by architect
        Joseph Paxton. Since it was built, there have been several additions to replace damage by bomb
        and fires.</string>

    <string name="market_variety">There are no shortage of options in the Market for visitors to
        choose from. From food to fashion, cooking, crafts, and jewellery, there\'s an incredible
        range of products to browse and buy.</string>

    <!-- Dark Arches category -->
    <string name="category_arches">Granary Wharf</string>

    <string name="dark_arches">The Dark Arches can be found under the Leeds Railway Station. They
        are lit by LEDs which slowly cycle through the rainbow spectrum, thereby adding colour to what
        would otherwise be a dark, cold, and foreboding place.</string>

    <string name="dark_arches_food">A few eateries can be found in the Dark Arches. From Italian to
        Tapas to your more traditional Yorkshire fare, if you\'re hungry or thirsty, this is a great place
        to go.</string>

    <string name="arches_and_wharf">Above the Dark Arches is Leeds Railway Station. Sitting in one of
        the venues there, you\'ll be able to hear the trains as they pass overhead. The Wharf contains
        two residential buildings, a hotel, and small cafés.</string>

    <string name="candle">Candle House is a residential building with a bar and restaurant in the base.
        Built in 2009, the building has won several design awards in part due to the \'twisting\' design
        which makes the building seem as though it\'s tilting.</string>

    <string name="arches_wharf_history">When the new railway station was built in 1866 (completed in 1869),
        the Dark Arches were created. Over 18 million bricks were used during the construction of the Arches.</string>


    <string name="list_item_image">list item image</string>
    <string name="test">TEST</string>
    <string name="map">map icon</string>

</resources>
